ABOUT ME

PhD/MSc/BSc in Computer Science and experience in machine learning techniques, deep learning, and web and API development. I have worked as a programmer and researcher and am skilled at adapting to different teams and environments.

LINK

github:

https://github.com/tgdulecha

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

ITALIAN

AMHARIC/AFAN OROMO

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth 30 Apr 1985

Nationality Ethiopian

PUBLICATIONS

DISK-NEURALRTI: OPTIMIZED NEURALRTI RELIGHTING THROUGH KNOWLEDGE DISTILLATION 2024

JAN 2024

NEURAL REFLECTANCE TRANSFORMATION IMAGING SYNTHPS: A BENCHMARK FOR EVALUATION OF PHOTOMETRIC STEREO **ALGORITHMS FOR CULTURAL HERITAGE APPLICATIONS** 2020 JAN 2020

TINSAE GEBRECHRISTOS DULECHA

POSTDOCTORAL RESEARCH FELLOW



Via francesco petrarca, 10, 30171, Venice, Italy, Venice, 30171, Italy



(+39) 3207256679



tinsae.gebrechristos@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

UNIVERSITY OF VERONA. **DEPARTMENT OF ENGINEERING FOR** INNOVATION **MEDICINE**

Verona Feb 2024 - Present

Research Fellow

• Researching material appearance, machine learning, and reflectance transformation imaging for cultural heritage applications.

CA' FOSCARI **UNIVERSITY OF VENICE**

Venice Feb 2023 - Jan 2024

Research Fellow

- Conducted research in the Department of Philosophy and Cultural Heritage.
- Realized an ARgument Extractor and Analyzer (AREA) a research tool that can extract and analyze arguments from online debates.

UNIVERSITY OF VERONA. **DEPARTMENT OF CULTURE AND CIVILIZATION**

Verona Sep 2021 - Jan 2023

Research Fellow

- I developed a web content management system that allowed the principal investigator to make edits.
- I designed and realized a database management system that enabled researchers to store, retrieve, and export archaeological data related to Roman emperors, from Augustus to the Tetrarchs.

UNIVERSITY OF VERONA. DEPARTMENT OF **COMPUTER SCIENCE**

Jan 2021 - Jun 2021

Research Scholarship Holder

• Conducted research in the field of Computer Science.

CA' FOSCARI **UNIVERSITY OF** VENICE, EUROPEAN **CENTRE FOR LIVING** TECHNOLOGY(ECLT)

Venice Oct 2016 - Oct 2017

HAWASSA UNIVERSITY. **INSTITUTE OF** TECHNOLOGY, SCHOOL OF **INFORMATICS**

Hawassa Mar 2016 - Oct 2016

Research Fellow

- Conducted research at the European Centre for Living Technology.
- Realized a computer vision system for beverage product recognition by analyzing refrigerator shelf images.

Lecturer

• Taught the laboratory sessions for the Introduction to Information Storage and Retrieval course using C++.

STATE-OF-THE-ART IN MULTI-LIGHT IMAGE COLLECTIONS FOR SURFACE VISUALIZATION AND ANALYSIS 2019

JAN 2019

CRACK DETECTION IN SINGLE-AND MULTI-LIGHT IMAGES OF PAINTED SURFACES USING CONVOLUTIONAL NEURAL NETWORKS 2019

JAN 2019

MLIC-SYNTHETIZER: A SYNTHETIC MULTI-LIGHT IMAGE COLLECTION GENERATOR 2019

JAN 2019

OBJECTIVE AND
SUBJECTIVE EVALUATION
OF VIRTUAL RELIGHTING
FROM REFLECTANCE
TRANSFORMATION
IMAGING DATA
2018
JAN 2018

ARTWORKS IN THE SPOTLIGHT: CHARACTERIZATION WITH A MULTISPECTRAL LED DOME 2017

JAN 2017

A COMPUTER VISION SYSTEM FOR THE AUTOMATIC INVENTORY OF A COOLER 2017

JAN 2017

REPLICATOR EQUATION: APPLICATIONS REVISITED 2017

JAN 2017

IUAV UNIVERSITY OF VENICE

Venice

Dec 2014 - Nov 2015

Research Fellow

- Conducted research at IUAV University of Venice.
- I worked on the development of a client-server augmented reality framework.

ETHIO TELECOM

Addis Ababa

Jan 2011 - Oct 2012

Pre-sales Engineer

 Provided technical advice and consulting for enterprise customers, prepared technical proposals, and implemented services.

ETHIOPIAN TELECOMMUNICATI ONS CORPORATION

Addis Ababa Sep 2007 - Oct 2011

Programmer

 Developed software for internal use of the company, and provided training for customer care and billing.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF VERONA

Verona 2021

PhD in Computer Science

 Focused on appearance measurement and analysis from multilight image collections using machine/deep learning techniques.

CA' FOSCARI UNIVERSITY OF VENICE

Venice 2014

Master of Science in Computer Science

 Studied Computer vision, Artificial Intelligence, Data and Web Mining, and other related subjects.

HAWASSA UNIVERSITY

Hawassa 2007

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

• Studied various courses in subjects areas such as software Development & Programming, Computer Science Core (Algorithms & Data Structures), Databases & Data Management, Networking & Systems Administration, Operating systems & computer architecture, Software Engineering & System Design, Mathematics & Theoretical Foundations, Artificial Intelligence & Advanced topics.

SKILLS

SCIKIT-LEARN, NUMPY, PANDAS, OPENCV SCIPY

PHP, FLASK, FASTAPI, ASP.NET CORE

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP

PYTHON, C++, MATLAB, JAVA

MS SQL SERVER, MYSQL

MATPLOTLIB, SEABORN

DOCKER, KUBERNETES

PYTORCH, KERAS